https://www.webteklabs.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAbout UsCoursesCareersBlogStudent AmbassadorContact Us
MENUMENUOnline CoursesMachine Learning using PythonDeep LearningPython with DjangoPython Programming LanguageData Science using Python & R ProgramingBig Data & HadoopData ScienceInternet of ThingsCloud Computing (AWS)C/C++ & Data StructuresProgramming Technique with C & C++Core Java with JavaFXAdvance Java with FrameworksFull stack Web development using J2EEFull Stack Development with Mongo DMASP.NET using C#Web Designing & Development using PHPPHPWeb Designing Using Angular JSKotlin With AndroidAndroid using JavaManual TestingSeleniumEthical Hacking Cyber Security
privacy policy
Online courses Weekdays / Weekends / Evening
Online courses Weekdays / Weekends / EveningOur instructor-led/offline courses are for entrepreneurs, working professionals & students. Make use of your evening, weekends or holidays to accelerate your career! Enroll with us
Register Here
Expert instruction Learn from Industry & MNC professionals
Expert instruction Learn from Industry & MNC professionals How about getting trained directly from industry leaders and MNC professionals? Yes, WebTek Labs makes it possible for you. Avail hands-on training and enhance your chance to get noticed by the top recruiters.
Register Here
Placement Courses Job oriented training with 100% placement asistance
Placement Courses Job oriented training with 100% placement asistanceWe don’t just promise; we provide what you promise. At WebTek Labs, we impart job-centric training and make you industry ready. Get assured placement assistance and even job interview scheduling with the top-notch companies.
Register Here
Global certificate Partnership with Oracle & Google
Global certificate Partnership with Oracle & Google WebTek Labs has gained recognition in the industry and it has entered into partnership with corporate giants such as Oracle and Google. We offer more than just training. We offer globally recognized certificate post-completion of the training course and help you to stand out in the crowd of competitors.
Register Here
Register for free workshops & events
Register for free workshops & eventsHurry up and book your seat for forthcoming workshops and events organized by us and you also do not have to pay a single penny!
Register Here
Home privacy policy
privacy policyEffective date: November 13, 2018WebTek Labs Pvt Ltd (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the www.webteklabs.com website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from www.webteklabs.comInformation Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberCookies and Usage DataUsage DataWe may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Use of DataWebTek Labs Pvt Ltd uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain the ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer care and supportTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the ServiceTo monitor the usage of the ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTransfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside India and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to India and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.WebTek Labs Pvt Ltd will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure Of DataLegal RequirementsWebTek Labs Pvt Ltd may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of WebTek Labs Pvt LtdTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilitySecurity Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=enLinks To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By email: info@webteklabs.comprivacy policy
Delhi Branch GN-12, 1st Floor, Shivaji Enclave, Rajouri Garden, New Delhi 110027, India Ph No.: +91-11- 45001 200/201, +91-8826008972
Kolkata Branch 4, Lee Road, Vaibhav Building, 5th Floor,Near Rabindra Sadan Metro Station, Kolkata 700 020, West Bengal.Contact: +91-9073332717, +91-9903049344
Kolkata Training Centre BD-44, Sector-1, Salt Lake, Near Tank Number-4,Kolkata 700-064, IndiaContact: +91-9831829641, +91-33-65011271
Hyderabad Centre Himayatnagar, HyderabadContact – 1800 212 4700
Jaipur Branch 1 Floor 264 Muktanand Nagar Gopalpura Bye Pass,Above Hdfc Bank Branch,Jaipur-302018Ph No.: +91-9354936793
Noida Branch iThum Tower B, 2nd Floor (B 205),Plot No A-40, Sector 62, Noida, Uttar Pradesh 201309 Ph No.: +91-0120-4261839, +91-9650599300
HomeAbout UsCoursesCareersOnline EnrollmentBlogStudent AmbassadorPrivacy PolicyContact Us
Copyright © 2020 webteklabs.com
Toll-Free 18002124700
Free Demo Call now
